Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Professor's
lab notes. final entry.
Time has been frozen for
an unknown length of time.
With no time to lose.
I began tunneling through time
in search of Fry and Leela.
only to find them suffering
from a case of extreme old.
Horrified. I offered
to reset the universe
to the instant
before time stopped.
They could be young once more.
Still grotesquely
ugly. but young.
- What do you say?
Wanna go around again?
- I do.
- D-Did someone switch
the universe off and on?
- It feels like we got rebooted!
- Ugh! Why is my beer stale?
Yay! I'm
sharing backwash with friends!
Well. whatever happened
the important thing is it
will never. ever happen...
again.
Robot?
- Nah. I'm just
yankin' your ass.
We're back. baby!
Good
news. everyone!
My new wrinkle
cream has arrived!
Also. we seem to have
survived a massive disruption
in the flow of time.
Did we get older? Younger?
Science holds no answers.
- Does science know
what year it is?
- Science knows everything!
Let's check the atomic calendar.
Hermes.
move that espresso maker out of
the way of the atomic calendar!
Good lord!
It's the year 3023!
- Finally. I thought he'd
never stop yammering.
Oh. I've only
just begun yammering!
I shall now expound
on the science of
explosive botulism.
- Have I really spent
23 years in the future?
- We call it the
present. but spluttever.
- Twenty-three years. and
I've achieved nothing.
Nothing!
- It's really sad. if you think about it.
- Yeah. Laugh all you want.
but I've wasted
enough of my life.
It's time I set myself a goal.
- Stop it!
- Ow!
But he said laugh all you want!
- I don't care. If Fry wants
to set a goal for himself.
we should support him.
not point and laugh.
Oh. right. I forgot to point.
Ow! ZOIDBERG: Ow.
Life's
goal. life's goal...
- Have you considered donating
your legs to the legless?
- Or destroying documents
for the shredder-less?
- Let's leave this up to Fry.
He just needs a little
peace and quiet.
Not on my watch!
- That's it! I've got my goal!
- And so quickly! What is it?
- J. Philip I. Fry.
I-I mean. I. Philip J. Fry.
hereby pledge to watch
every TV show ever made!
I don't know. meatbag.
There's a mighty deep
diaper of content out there.
- I eat diapers for breakfast.
It'll take a lot of sitting.
but with the world's fourth-most
popular streaming service.
I can do it.
I'm subscribing to...
Fulu!
- Leela. aren't you
gonna stop this?
- I should. but I don't
wanna crush his dreams.
Hermes. can you
crush his dreams?
- Oh. no. You're not fobbing
that girlfriend duty off on me.
- A lifetime of laziness
gives me a huge head start.
Watched
it. Watched it.
Hate-watched it.
Hate-watched it twice.
- Kif has a single
friend. His name is Zapp.
- Stop. I said I would
support Fry's dumb goal.
and I will.
I say go for it.
- Thanks. Leela. Ooh!
The Scary Mirror!
That sounds scary.
You're entering
a show that is slightly different
from previous. very
similar shows.
What was once a creepy
story about a book
is now about an E-reader
that's too greasy to hold.
And that one with the
phone call from the devil?
Now. it's a FaceTime
call from the devil.
The devil part didn't
change.
Prepare to see your
unflattering reflection in...
The Scary Mirror.
- Hey. Sniri! Get
off your fat squiggle
and make me a dinner reservation
at Impassable Burger!
And check the price of my NFTs
'cause I'm an important tech guy!
Reservation
confirmed. NFTs worthless.
- What?! You shoulda told me to sell
them! Any idiot could do your job!
What the hell. Sniri?
From now on. I'll be
asking the stupid questions.
Such as. "What's the weather
right outside my damn window?"
And. um. "How does a
steering wheel work?"
- Wow. Whatever just happened
really makes you think.
- It sure do.
TV. dumb it down for me.
- Bam!
- Aw...
What is the
deal with non-binary robots?
Wow. PC Crowd.
- Without Fry's interruptions.
efficiency is up
32 perc... Mm...
- Well. my butt's numb.
and my remote hand is dead.
but all I have left is the
final season of All My Circuits.
- Which final season? They got
canceled. like. three or four times.
- Pfft! Loserama!
- The final final season.
from 10 years ago.
I wonder how many
episodes were in it?
- Mm. twelve... No. Thirteen...
thousand and twenty.
- 13.020? But... But...
I'll never make it!
I'm sorry. Leela.
I'll never be able to watch
enough TV to make you proud of me.
It might
actually be possible.
But... No.
- What? What is it?
- It's risky. but we
have a technology now
that allows you to
watch all the episodes
in one continuous stretch.
We call it... bingeing.
No. no! [gasps] What?
- Sounds great! I'll do it!
- You don't understand. Fry!
Bingeing doesn't mean
what it did in your day!
- Drinking two six-packs and
barfing in my mom's jewelry box?
- Ew! No! It means strapping
into these bingeing goggles
that drill directly
into your brain.
- Fry. don't be
the idiot you are.
Before you go jabbing
into your visual cortex.
I implore you to...
Ow! My cortex!
- I maintain that this is
a catastrophically
boneheaded idea.
But. if you're going to binge.
you'll need a still suit.
- Why is it called a still suit?
- Because you'll be
sitting perfectly still.
And I can't have you
soiling my binge-a-lounger.
- Engage hoses!
- I'm not entirely sure
which is the air hose
and which is the waste hose.
But. live and
learn.
- Farewell. Leela.
And always remember...
♪ All My Circuits
organ theme playing ♪
All My Circuits
is brought to you by...
Honey Bunches of Springs.
Everybody loves Honey
Bunches of Springs!
Except humans.
Fatal for humans.
- Calculon! But you weren't due back
from the time travel convention until...
- Yesterday?!
- He's been streaming for
months without a single break.
- No wonder you find
him so attractive.
- The waste buckets indicate
strong bowel function.
Now. let's see how his
brain is holding up
to this sensory assault.
Oh. dear.
- Is that the TV signal
or Fry's brainwaves?
- Both!
Fry's feeble mind has been
overpowered by the binge.
He's losing touch with reality!
It's true!
He's not responding to any of
the sounds or smells I'm making.
- As long as Fry doesn't run
out of episodes. he'll be okay.
But if he reaches the end
of the series. God forbid.
his consciousness
will be severed!
Much as this hedge clipper
severs Leela's ponytail.
- Hey!
- Oh. boo-hoo!
It's a metaphor. Don't
take it literally.
- But. Fry will
become a vegetable!
- Yum! I mean sad.
- This is all my fault.
Actually. it's
mostly Fry's fault.
but it's a little my fault!
- We have to find some way
to extricate Fry from
Fulu's iron grip.
I'll put on my thinking cap.
- There's not much time.
He's almost out of episodes
of All My Circuits.
- Maybe they'll
drop a new season.
- Eh. fat chance. sweatpants.
It got canceled 10 years ago.
TV shows don't come
back after that. No way!
Not on broadcast or cable.
- What about Fulu? They'll
bring back any old crap!
Good thinking!
Maybe we can get them to reboot
it as a streaming series.
- We'll start a fan campaign.
with letters and a viral hashtag!
- Pfft. That's a recipe for
failure. Let's go punch somebody.
- Have a good one.
- Tell us why you think
you can punch your way
into the Fulu executive suite.
- And if we can
validate your parking.
- Alright. Here's our pitch.
Remember that show
All My Circuits?
- The one that got
canceled three times?
- Exactly!
New episodes of that!
That's our pitch.
- Conferencing.
I'm going to have to say...
- Hard.
- Pass.
- All My Circus reruns have
a devoted robot fan base.
but they rarely buy anything
from our advertisers.
- Correction. New data
indicates a sudden uptick
in buying by viewers.
- Correction. One viewer.
- Sweet jerk venison
of Turkmenistan!
Fry ordered all this junk?
Robot cereal. Robot noodles.
Robot oil. Oh.
wait. That's mine.
- So. what do you say?
How about picking up All My
Circuits for 20 episodes?
- With an option for 20 more!
- Maybe a movie?
- Hm. Against my better
judgment programing.
I'm going to greenlight
the project.
- Woo-hoo!
- Points on the back end!
- Now. there's one teensy hitch.
You know the star of the
show. Calculon? He's dead.
- Everything is negotiable.
- Hell yes. you can
have him! Scale plus 10.
And if he dies
again. no backsies.
Hey. Calculon! CALCULON: Yes?
- You're wanted on set!
- Oh. glorious rapture.
To return to the draped
proscenium once more...
- Will you shut up and get
into the resurrection cannon?
- Alright. it's great to be back.
Truly humbled. All the usual crap.
Places. everyone! Places!
- Ah...
Where is my assistant? I
need help finding my mark.
- Uh. I'm Mark.
More coffee. Mr. Calculon?
- Yes. I do need to
expel more coffee.
Professor
to Hollywood. Come in. Hollywood.
- Talk to me. How many
episodes does Fry have left?
- Two. And one of
them is a clip show.
- But that means...
- Indeed. If you don't crank
out new episodes quickly.
Fry will be dead by lunch.
I'm having ham salad.
- But. this is impossible. To
keep them from running out.
we'll need to produce an
hour-long episode every hour.
nonstop. forever!
- If Law & Order can
do it. so can you.
Professor out!
Futurama is
brought to you by...
- Slurm Zero! None
of the flavor.
all of the addiction!
Whimmy-wham-wham-wozzle!
- Monique. my love.
Will you be my...
- Cut! Next episode! Action!
Plumber?
- Fry better not be
puttin' this robot junk
on the corporate credit card.
That's exclusively for my
one-man business dinners.
- Hermes. quit your low-stakes
embezzling and look at this.
Fry is now streaming
at double speed!
I'll mirror his view on the TV.
Oh. how
I love the illicit thrill
of cheating on my husband with
an actual flesh-and-blood human.
A filthy. filthy human.
So squishy and gooey.
You're like a sexy
water balloon.
The
thrill is all mine. Monique.
I've never been on
a swan boat before.
Calculon!
Monique. how
could you? And with Human Friend.
the very person I've been
cheating on you with.
Calculon. how could you?
And with Human Friend. the very
person I've been cheating on you with.
- Calculon. Monique. how could you?
- Enough. We're stuck in a loop.
- I just hope we can
come to some agreement.
and that this boat can
hold six tons of steel.
- He's streaming at double
speed? Why not just slow it down?
- Because Fry's brain is in a
very precarious binge-state.
Any change. even refilling the
Dorito bowl. could kill him.
Oh. no! PROFESSOR : Oh. yes.
You've got to make
episodes faster. Faster!
- We're already making an
hour-long show every hour.
That's the fastest
it can be done!
Nonsense. Leela.
Why. I am the spokesman
for fast acting.
- You're the spokesman for
fast-acting hemorrhoid cream.
- Your point?
- I have none.
- A robot actor of my
caliber can act at speeds
far beyond what even the greatest
human actors can achieve.
To be or not to be.
That is the question.
Whether 'tis nobler in the
mind to suffer the slings and arrows...
- You missed a line.
- Can you direct
at double speed?
- I don't know. Can you
pay at double scale?
It's not my money. Just
yell action really. really fa...
- Action!
Calculon.
I've come to tell you that...
- Um...
- Cut! What happened?
- The script pages stopped uploading.
- It's those damned lazy writers!
Can't even manage to write an
hour-long episode every 15 minutes.
- I died doing what I hated.
- Can't you just ad lib?
- Asking an actor to ad
lib is like asking a...
guy to... five.
So I'll just
write the scripts.
- Any idiot could be a TV
writer. - Many are.
- How hard can it be?
I love you. Calculon.
Let's do it. baby.
Bender is great.
And fade to black.
- You're hired!
- Hello. Writer's Guild.
I'm afraid
he'll never calculate again.
- Or he'll do so inaccurately.
- Let's do it. baby.
- Bender is great.
- Cut!
Okay. reset for scene 31.652B...
- Was that heart attack
part of the script?
No. but leave it in. It's hilarious.
- Fry's life is on the line.
It's all up to me as
executive producer.
Action! I mean. action!
Louder and funnier!
Smile faster!
Act
better! Less nuance!
That was terrible! Next scene!
Action! Cut! Action! I mean.
cut!
Action! And... cut!
- Wow. Great writing.
everyone. That's a wrap!
What exactly happened in that episode?
I won an
Emmy. that's what.
Okay. everyone.
take five... seconds. Next episode!
- Hang on. Leela.
I think the execubots have
some constructive notes.
- This is very hard for me to
say. Leela. so he'll say it.
- We love everything about this
show. It's not working at all.
You're canceled.
- You'll always be an important
part of the Fulu family.
Get out!
- But. our friend Fry...
He's gonna die...
- Strike the set.
How does a
show get canceled
this many times?
By this many networks?!
- Bad news. Professor.
They won't let us make
any more episodes.
- That is bad news.
Especially since I
have... good news!
Kidnap the actors and
get back here at once!
Fry's down to the
very last episode.
but he still has one slim hope.
We've got to gradually
shift his focus
from the streaming world
back to the real world.
- Is that safe?
- God. no!
While he watches
the finale on Fulu.
you'll simultaneously perform
it live in front of him.
- You're asking me to
perform a second take?
- No. no!
Think of it as live theater for
one unconscious audience member.
- Ah. like the Milwaukee
Shakespeare Festival.
- Exactly!
And action.
Easing Fry back
to normal viewing speed.
Now. we'll gradually
decrease the opacity
of his bingeing goggles.
Gently... Gently...
- Monique. Boxy.
the feelings between each
distinct subset of two of us
are too intense to bear.
We find ourselves the vertices
of a classic love triangle.
- It's a three-variable
equation with only one solution.
X equals suicide.
- Does this love triangle
have room for one more vertex?
- Technically. yes.
though it would then
constitute a love tetrahedron.
Allow me to illustrate
with a model.
Bringing Fry back to reality in three...
Two...
- Hey. where'd I put my cigar?
Zounds!
Thank you... Milwaukee.
- Somebody other
than me do something!
- I'll put out the fire!
- No! That's battery acid!
- Oops.
- He's dead!
I killed him by encouraging
his hopes and dreams!
How could I have
been so stupid?!
- What up?
- I'm afraid I
have bad news. Fry.
You're dead.
- I am?
- Fry! You weren't in the suit?
- What? No.
I got out of that thing.
like. two days ago.
I decided to catch
up on my reading.
I'm sorry. Leela.
You must be pretty
disappointed in me.
- No. I'm just glad you're okay.
And I promise I'll never
be supportive again.
- Thanks. Leela.
You know. I really did
try to achieve my goal.
I even turned up the
playback to double speed.
but I just couldn't get
through the last few episodes.
I mean. they were unwatchable.
The writing and the executive producing
really went downhill towards the end.
- Hey. I may not
be a great writer.
but at least I filled
the allotted air time.
To the second. Fade to black.
- We now go live
to the White House
for the presidential summit on the
dangers of streaming television.
- I understand it's
destroying our young people.
That is my job!
- Aroo!
Now. Mr. Fry. I understand
you recently endured
a terrible ordeal while
doing something stupid
involving streaming television.
- That's right. Your Majesty.
- And what lesson. if
any. did you learn?
- Well. first. I guess.
don't reboot a show if the
quality isn't gonna be there.
But. more importantly.
let me say this.
Viewers must binge responsibly.
The same way they smoke
cigarettes or drink bleach.
In my opinion. they must stream
no more than 10
episodes in a row.
And no less.
But it's not just the
viewers' responsibility.
Any TV show that truly
cares about its audience.
that loves and respects
them. should...
no... must be canceled
every few years.
It's simply the
right thing to do.
Thank you.
- Sobering thoughts from
some drug-addled weirdo.
Goodnight. God bless Earth.
and aroo.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm